virginmango.com 2014-02-14

# Privacy Policy | VirginMango.com

_**VIRGIN MANGO- PRIVACY POLICY**_

VIRGINMANGO respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that access the information and use the services brought through them. Individually identifiable information about you is not willfully disclosed to any third party without first receiving your permission, as covered in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy describes VIRGINMANGO’s treatment of personally identifiable information that VIRGINMANGO collects when you are on the VIRGINMANGO’s website.  

 **1\. Changes to Privacy Policy**  

We review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. The revisions in Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon being posted on the Website. Therefore, you may wish periodically review this page to make sure you have the latest version.   

**  
2\. Information You Give Us:**  

We receive and store any information you enter on our Websites or give in any other way (e.g., by telephone). This may include information you provide when you register as a member (either directly or through Face book or any other Social website or any other way), engage in transactions, search, contact customer service, or participate in contests, promotions, surveys, forums, content submissions, chats, bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions or other aspects or services offered by us. As a result, you may be supplying us with information such as your name, address, and phone numbers; and other billing information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; names and e-mail addresses of friends and possible referrals and other people. All online payment transactions are done at the payment gateway site (we use more than one payment gateway). The payment gateways that we have tied up with are affiliated with established banking institutions and follow guidelines that are published and monitored by the Reserve Bank of India.  

 **3. Do we use cookies?**  

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information   
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  

 **We Categories information about you (collectively referred to as "Personal Information") as follows:**  
 **(a) Profiling Information: We collect your Profiling and Account Information for the following reasons:** (a) we need your identity details, contact details, banking information and account history to manage our relationship with you and provide Services to you. We may use this information for suggesting products that you might like on our website. We will only disclose this information was provided below. (b) We use certain of your information in an aggregated form to compile statistical and demographical profiles for our business and marketing activities. We may disclose such information about you, provided that the information is in an aggregated form that is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you. 2.2 We collect and store your Service Usage and Transactional Information to: (a) determine and verify the Service Charges payable by you and to administer our relationship with you. (b) Comply with any statutory or regulatory requirement. (c) Compile statistical and demographical profiles about you for our business and marketing activities and to customize our Services to you. While we are entitled to use such information about you for our own internal business purposes without limitation, we will only disclose it in an aggregated form which is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you; and (d) monitor your use of our Services for the purposes of ensuring compliance with our Terms of use. 2.3 We collect and store your Correspondence Information and Personal Identifiers to: (a) comply with our obligations under law; and (b) monitor your use of our Services in order to ensure your compliance with our Terms of use. Any Personal Information which we collect and which we may use in an aggregated format ensuring you are not individually identified is our property. We may use it, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including (without limitation) the commercial sale thereof to third parties   
(c) Service Usage: Information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads. (d) Log information: Information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request. (e) Transactional Information: Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities. (f) Correspondence Information: Content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services, which include email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, experts forum communications, fax mail communications, membership of mailing lists etc. (g) User IDs: Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services. (h) Stored Information: Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc. We only collect your Personal Information to conduct our business and to enable us to deliver and improve our Services. We do not for any reason whatsoever sell your Personal Information to any third party or otherwise trade on it.   

**(d) Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this Information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other issues.  

 **  
(e) Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites  

 **(f) Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.   

**(h)Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

**4.   GENERAL EXCEPTIONS**

If we are required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store your Personal Information: (a) by law; (b) to conduct our business; (c) to secure our systems; or (d) to enforce our own rights, we will do so in the manner as prescribed by law. Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we will not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage. In order to ensure that all our Users comply with the Terms of use, we may monitor your Personal Information to the extent that this may be required to determine compliance and/or to identify instances of non-compliance. To ensure that the security and integrity of our Services are safeguarded, we may monitor your Personal Information. This monitoring may include (without limitation) the filtering of incoming and outgoing electronic data messages to identify, limit and/or prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content. We may under certain circumstances procure an element of the Services from a third party service provider. To the extent that it may be necessary, and solely for the purposes of providing the Service to you, you agree that we may disclose to such third party any of your Personal Information that may be necessary for the procurement of services from the third Party  

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below and by using our site, you consent to our privacy policy  

 **Payment Gateway Disclaimer**

Payments done by you to VIRGIN MANGO may be through an electronic and automated collection and remittance service (the “Payment Gateway”) through ICICI Bank and Citrus Payment Solutions Pvt. Ltd, Atom Technologies Ltd and Times of Money (the ‘Payment Service Providers’). The Payment Gateway service is provided to you in order to facilitate easy payments for registration and course fees. VIRGIN MANGO makes no representation of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the Payment Gateway. You expressly agree that your use of this online payment service is entirely at your own risk.
